https://www.asatonline.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentNews & EventsNewsletter SignupFacebook page opens in new windowTwitter page opens in new windowInstagram page opens in new window(Google Translate Disclaimer)Search:
Search
Autism TreatmentParents & EducatorsWhat is Autism?Autism DiagnosisSpecific TreatmentsSavvy ConsumerLifespan ResourcesMedical ProfessionalsSupport to FamiliesRegulating SleepFood SelectivityToilet TrainingBowel TrainingMouthing ObjectsDental ExamsNeighborhood SafetyAdolescents Safety SkillsReview of Mortality in Autism DrowningReview of Healthcare for Children on the Autism SpectrumPreparing to Speak with a Doctor About MedicationDiscussing Concerns with Family MembersMedical ResearchMethylphenidate in PDD with HyperactivityLack of Efficacy of CitalopramMedication & Parent TrainingAutism Treatment Reviews for PhysiciansReview of The Complete Guide to Autism TreatmentsReview of Do You Believe in Magic?Autism TreatmentsBiomedical InterventionsPsychological, Educational, & Therapeutic InterventionsInterventions Addressing Core DeficitsDevelopmental Interventions – Other Research ModelsPractitioners GuidanceEarly Detection & InterventionAutism & Intellectual DisabilityRecurrence of Autism in FamiliesEncouraging Parent Participation in Home-Based InterventionEthics & Evidence-based PracticeTransition Resources for Adolescents and AdultsIncorporating Occupational TherapyMediaOverviewHow Can We Help You?FAQs for the MediaContact UsResourcesQuestions to Ask Before Writing The Next StoryFostering Positive Portrayals of Science-based Autism Treatment in the MediaAutism Treatment in the MediaMedia WatchAbout Media WatchArchived LettersAbout UsMissionHistoryAccomplishmentsBoard of DirectorsScience in Autism Treatment Publication TeamProfessional Advisory BoardStaff & VolunteersContact UsGet InvolvedVolunteeringExternship ProgramPublic AwarenessFundraisingFinancial SupportResearch & TreatmentResourcesTopical ArticlesBook & Resources ReviewsResearch SynopsesInterviewsPerspectivesThe BookshelfApplying Science to EducationExcellence in Special EducationVideosOutside ResourcesEvaluating ResearchTreatmentClinical CornerLearn More About Specific TreatmentsMaking Sense of Autism Treatments: Weighing the EvidenceSavvy ConsumerConferencesNewsletterSubscribeLatest IssueArchivesAdvertise with usPrivacy PolicyYou are here:HomePrivacy PolicyASAT respects the privacy of those who visit our website. ASAT does not collect information about its visitors for commercial marketing. If you choose to provide us with personal information, as in an e-mail to info@ASATonline.org, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through our web site, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us provide the information you have requested. We do not create individual profiles with the information you provide.While ASAT may collect certain non-identifiable information about visitors to this site, we do not link IP addresses to any personal information associated with the individual visitor. ASAT uses this non-identifiable information only to determine how to make future visits to our site more convenient, engaging and productive by collecting anonymous information such as:Your IP address (a unique number assigned to very computer that connects to the Internet);Your domain type (e.g., .ca, .com, .net or .org);Standard information included with every communication sent on the Internet, such as browser type, geographical location, referral URL, operating system, service provider and local time.Cookies saved by the browser log what style sheet is being used by the viewer (e.g., high contrast, large text, normal contrast, medium text).We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors, to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record personal information about individuals and their visits.ASAT’s web site and materials may contain hypertext or links to other Internet computer sites which are not owned, operated, controlled or reviewed by ASAT. These links are provided solely as a courtesy and convenience to you, the visitor. When you link to one of these sites, you are no longer on ASAT’s web site and this Privacy Notice will not apply. When you link to another web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site. Love This Share Share Tweet Pin EmailSuggested PagesWhat is autism?
Get the factsHeard about a treatment?
Find out the scientific community’s view about itWhat does the research say?
Read our research summaries Want to understand how to weigh the evidence? Make sense of autism treatmentsWhat do other professional groups have to say about specific treatments?
Read task force findingsHow do you tell the difference between something that works and something that doesn’t?
Become a savvy consumerWant to hear what leaders in the field of autism have to say?
Read the interviews sectionQuestion about specific issues?
Ask a professionalLooking for a newsletter to keep you up to date?
Read our latest newsletter Support Real Science
in Autism TreatmentDONATE TODAYGo to Top
Send this to a friendYour emailRecipient emailSendCancel
